Finding Aid for Vice President for Government Relations (University of Michigan) records, 1960-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files, 1961-1999
  - 1968-1994
    - Michigan Education Trust, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
    - Michigan Technology Council, 1990 (Box 20)
    - Michigan Technology Network, 1986-1992 (Box 20)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Michigan Department of Commerce, 1984-1992 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Department of Corrections, 1976-1989 (Box 20)
      - Governor's Office, 1976-1993 (Box 20)
      - Commission on the Future of Higher Education, 1981-1988; 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Michigan Department of Natural Resources, 1991-1994 (Box 20)
      - State Legislature, 1991-1994; 6 folders (Box 20)
      - State Legislature, 1973-1990; 20 folders (Box 21)
    - Moore, Edward F. (donor of funds to the university through his Foundation for the Future of Man, Inc.), 1972-1986 (Box 21)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1989-1994 (Box 21)
    - Pellerito, Pete (Assistant to VP Kennedy), 1984-1994; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Plant Extension Committee Capital Outlay Requests, 1986-1991 (Box 22)
    - Power, Philip, 1984-1994 (Box 22)
    - Racism on Campus, 1987-1988; 2 folders
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2018; removed to vault]
    - Regents' Correspondence, 1969-1989; 17 folders (Box 22)
    - Replacement Hospital Project, 1979-1986 (Box 22)
    - Role of the University (Mission Statements), 1976-1989 (Box 22)
    - Rose Bowl, 1979-1993 (Box 22)
    - Rutgers University (external review of Government Relations/Community Affairs departments), 1987-1988 (Box 22)
    - Sea Grant Program, 1974; 1978 (Box 22)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration (the University of Michigan and State of Michigan), 1986-1987 (Box 22)
    - Shapiro, Harold, 1979-1988 (Box 23)
    - South Africa (regarding the University's policy toward), 1979-1986 (Box 23)
    - Speeches
      - Alumni Groups, 1980-1993 (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1971-1992 (Box 23)
      - Other Universities, 1982-1989 (Box 23)
      - State Governments, 1976-1990 (Box 23)
      - University Functions, 1976-1987 (Box 23)
    - State Building Authority, 1976-1989 (Box 23)
    - Student Organizations, 1988-1994 (Box 23)
    - State Relations Officers Committee, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Statewide House Officers Training, 1975-1977 (Box 23)
    - Superior Township Technology Center, 1983-1989 (Box 23)
    - University Events Task Force, 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    - University Hospital, 1976-1982 (Box 23)
    - University Relations Task Force, 1968 (Box 23)
  - 1980-1997
    The Topical Files,1980-1997 (4.0 linear feet), are similar to the Washington office files, but tend to focus more on the duties of the Government Relations Office in Ann Arbor and mainly reflect monitoring and lobbying issues prior to the establishment of a permanent university office in Washington, D.C. in 1990. The majority of these files are from the 1980s. The series also documents the involvement of the University of Michigan in national higher education associations, particularly the Association of American Universities (AAU) and the National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC).
    - Academic Research Facilities, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Access to Health Care Insurance, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Accounting Standards, 1986-1987 (Box 34)
    - Accrediting Regulations, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Accrued Vacation Time, 1987 (Box 34)
    - Ad Hoc Tax Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 34)
    - AIDS Research (June Osborn), 1988-1989 (Box 34)
    - Alumni Club of Washington, DC, 1987-1989 (Box 34)
    - American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business (AACSB), 1987-1989 (Box 34)
    - American Council on Education, 1981-1988; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Archivist Appointment (National Archivist), 1986 (Box 34)
    - Association for Institutional Research Conference, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU)
      - 1983-1988 (Box 34)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 34)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 34)
      - Graduate Education Working Group, 1985 (Box 34)
      - Taxation of Tuition Benefits, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Blanchard Student Aid Proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Budget and Appropriations, 1981-1985; 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Bush Foundation Child Centers, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Butts, Tom-General Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 34)
    - Campus Compact, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Charitable Contributions, 1989-1990 (Box 34)
    - Chemical/ Biological Laboratories, 1988 (Box 34)
    - Chicago Desegregation Case, 1983-1987; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - CIESEN-Global Change, 1990-1994 (Box 34)
    - Collections Testimony: House Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Computer Virus Legislation, 1989 (Box 34)
    - COREtech
      - 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Coalition for Advancing Industrial Technology, 1986-1987 (Box 34)
      - Lobbying, 1990-1992 (Box 34)
      - Taxation, 1987-1988 (Box 34)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, 1982-1984 (Box 34)
    - Crockett, Larry, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Default Prevention Bill, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Defense Proposal-Shapiro, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Democratic Party Higher Education Task Force, 1982 (Box 35)
    - Dental Trust Fund, 1994 (Box 35)
    - Draft Registration Amendment, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Duderstadt, James, Washington Visits, 1986-1988 (Box 35)
    - Education Amendments, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Educational Leadership Center, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Educational Resource Information Center (ERIC), 1986-1987 (Box 35)
    - Election Results, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Employee Education Assistance, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Employee Education Assistance Act, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Employee Education Assistance Coalition, 1986-1988 (Box 35)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Ship, Bay City, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Export Bill, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Facilities-Ed Fox and M. Fuqua, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Facilities Lobbying, 1983-1985 (Box 35)
    - Facilities Reauthorization, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Federal Legislative Advisory Group (FLAG), 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Federal Tax Proposals, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Financial Aid Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Ford, William D., 1986-1991 (Box 35)
    - Fringe Benefits, 1984-1988 (Box 35)
    - GEAR-Flint, 1992 (Box 35)
    - Gifts of Appreciated Property, 1990 (Box 35)
    - Government Affairs Oversight Committee, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Graduate Student Loan Defaults, 1988 (Box 35)
    - Gramm-Rudman, 1985-1986 (Box 35)
    - Guaranteed Student Loans, 1981-1988 (Box 35)
    - Health Professions Manpower, 1981-1984 (Box 35)
    - Hertel Hearing on Postsecondary Education, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Higher Education Act (HEA) Reauthorization
      - 1983-1985 (Box 35)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 35)
      - 1985 (Box 35)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 36)
      - 1986-1997 (Box 36)
      - Conferences, 1992-1998 (Box 36)
      - Part H, 1993-1997 (Box 36)
      - Title I, 1983-1986 (Box 36)
      - Title IV, 1983-1997 (Box 36)
      - Title VI, 1983-1997; 8 folders (Box 36)
      - Title IX, 1995-1997 (Box 36)
      - Title X, 1996 (Box 36)
    - Higher Education Coalition for the Research and Development Tax Credit, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Higher Education Disclosure Act, 1985-1986 (Box 36)
    - Human Development Service Programs, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Immigration Legislation, 1982-1984 (Box 36)
    - Indian (Native American) Artifacts, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Indirect Costs, 1994-1995 (Box 36)
    - Institute of Science and Technology, 1988 (Box 36)
    - Insurance-Sex Discrimination, 1983 (Box 36)
    - International Education, 1983-1990 (Box 36)
    - International Society for Heart Research Soviet Visa, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Jobs Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
    - Legislators (correspondence with), 1985-1991; 4 folders (Box 36)
    - Libraries, 1988 (Box 37)
    - Lobby Registration Act, 1984-1989 (Box 37)
    - Mandatory Retirement, 1986-1988 (Box 37)
    - Martin Luther King Day Symposium, 1987 (Box 37)
    - Michigan Parent Loan Program, 1981 (Box 37)
    - Michigan Student Financial Aid Association
      - 1986 (Box 37)
      - Conference, 1988 (Box 37)
    - Michigan Tax Information Council, 1986 (Box 37)
    - National Advisory Council on Continuing Education, 1986 (Box 37)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1984-1989; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - National Graduate Fellowships, 1985-1987 (Box 37)
    - National Institute of Education, 1984-1986 (Box 37)
    - National Institute of Health, 1983 (Box 37)
    - National Science Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 37)
    - National Student Aid Coalition Committee on Needs Assessment and Delivery, 1984 (Box 37)
    - National Trust for Higher Education, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Natural Gas Policy, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Negotiated Rule Making
      - 1992 (Box 37)
      - 1994 (Box 37)
    - Program Integrity, 1992 (Box 37)
    - Research and Development, 1984-1986 (Box 37)
    - Shelby Bill, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Southeast Asia Center, 1982-1984 (Box 37)
    - Soviet-East European Bills, 1983 (Box 37)
    - State Secondary Markets, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Student Loans, 1979-1990; 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Student Loan Defaults, 1987-1989 (Box 37)
    - TA Research Costs, 1996-1997 (Box 37)
    - Tax Exempt Bonds, 1984-1987 (Box 37)
    - Tax Issues
      - 1984-1986 (Box 37)
      - 1997 (Box 37)
    - Tax Monitoring Group, 1982-1987 (Box 37)
    - Tax Reform Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 37)
    - Tax Reform Act of, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Taxation-Tuition Waivers, 1985-1986 (Box 37)
    - Testimony on Education, Arts and Humanities, 1987 (Box 37)
    - University of Michigan
      - Basketball Team at the White House, 1989 (Box 37)
      - Financial Disaster Planning, 1981-1982 (Box 37)
      - Impact Data, 1981-1983 (Box 37)
      - Office of Academic Affairs Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 37)
      - School of Dentistry, 1988 (Box 37)
      - Student Financial Aid, 1981-1983 (Box 37)
- Office Assignments and Communications Records, 1969-1979
  Office Assignments and Communication Records, 1969 to 1979 (4.0 linear feet), consists of two principle files: Assignments and Communication and Trip Records. The Assignments files is subdivided into files for 1976-1977 and 1977-1978. Both of these runs of files are alphabetically arranged, and cover a wide variety of topics, nearly all of them budget-related.
  The Communication and Trip Records file is arranged chronologically, and then alphabetically within the span of years. These files document the liaison communications and visits between the Office of the Vice President for Government Relations and Secretary of the University and various agencies of the state of Michigan, such as the Bureau of the Budget, Department of Education, and the House and Senate Fiscal Agencies.
  - 1969-1979
    - Annual Reports, Internal, 1975/76; 1976/77 (Box 11)
    - Assignments
      - 1976-1977
        - American Association of University Professors (Box 11)
        - Analysis of Funding Models for President's Council Retreat (Box 11)
        - Appropriations Acts Comparisons (Box 11)
        - Arts Information Request (Box 11)
        - Average Family Income (Box 11)
        - Budget Terms (Box 11)
        - Compensation Data (Box 11)
        - Continuing Education in Funding Model (Box 11)
        - Cost Study Summary (Box 11)
        - Dental Funding (Box 11)
        - Economic Factors-1977/78 Budget Request (Box 11)
        - Enrollment Data (Box 11)
        - Glazer Project (Box 11)
        - Higher Education Funding Model Task Force, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Instruction-Research/Relation Test (Box 11)
        - Inventory (Box 11)
        - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 11)
        - Medical-General (Box 11)
        - Medical Instruction Cost Parameters (Box 11)
        - Mental Health Unit Appropriations Analysis (Box 11)
        - Michigan Medical/Osteopathic Schools Cost Study (Box 11)
        - Midwest Educational Compact (Box 11)
        - Pittsburgh Planning Questionnaire (Box 11)
        - Pre-Pharmacy Program (Box 11)
        - Private Giving (Box 11)
        - Proposal C (Box 11)
        - Revenue Forecasting (Box 11)
        - Role and Mission Statement (Box 11)
        - Sunset Legislation (Box 11)
        - Title I (Box 11)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 12)
        - Academic Program Inventory (Box 12)
        - Reciprocal States Tuition Agreement (Box 12)
        - State Aid to Private Colleges (Box 12)
        - Tax Limitation Proposal Analysis (Box 12)
        - Telephone Usage (Box 12)
        - University Television Center (Box 12)
        - Workshop Management Materials (Box 12)
    - Communication and Trip Records
      - 1970-1971
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of the Budget
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 12)
          - Legislative Fiscal Agency
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
        - Trip Records, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - 1971-1972
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of Programs and Budget
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
          - Department of Education (Box 12)
          - General, 2 folders (Box 12)
          - House Fiscal Agency
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
          - Legislative Fiscal Agency
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
        - Trip Records, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - 1972-1973
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of Programs and Budget
            - Incoming (Box 12)
            - Outgoing (Box 12)
          - Department of Education (Box 12)
          - General (Box 12)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 13)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 13)
        - Trip Records, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - 1973-1974
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of Programs and Budget
            - Incoming (Box 13)
            - Outgoing (Box 13)
          - Department of Education (Box 13)
          - General
            - Incoming (Box 13)
            - Outgoing (Box 13)
          - House Fiscal Agency
            - Incoming (Box 13)
            - Outgoing (Box 13)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 13)
      - 1973-1974
        (cont.)
        - Trip Records, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
      - 1974-1975
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of the Budget (Box 13)
          - Department of Education (Box 13)
          - General, 2 folders (Box 13)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 13)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 13)
        - Trip Records, 4 folders (Box 13)
      - 1975-1976
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of the Budget (Box 13)
          - Department of Education (Box 13)
          - General (Box 13)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
        - Trip Records, 5 folders (Box 14)
      - 1976-1977
        - Communication Records
          - Department of Education (Box 14)
          - General (Box 14)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
          - Office of the Budget (Box 14)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
        - Trip Records, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - 1977-1978
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of the Budget (Box 14)
          - Department of Education (Box 14)
          - General (Box 14)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
        - Trip Records, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - 1978-1979
        - Communication Records
          - Bureau of the Budget (Box 14)
          - Dearborn Campus (Box 14)
          - Department of Education (Box 14)
          - General (Box 14)
          - House Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
          - Intra-University (Box 14)
          - Lansing-General (Box 14)
          - Senate Fiscal Agency (Box 14)
        - Trip Records (Box 14)
- Special Topical Files, 1982-1994
  The materials in the Special Topical Files series, 1982-1994 (2.0 linear feet), differ from materials in the Topical Files series as the subjects here are primarily budget related. The series contains correspondence between the Vice President for Government Relations office and legislative bodies such as the Department of Management and Budget, the House Fiscal Agency, and House and Senate Appropriations committees. Other topics of interest are budget concerns of the Dearborn and Flint campuses, the Governor's budget recommendations, and the Research Excellence Fund applications submitted by various departments on campus.
  - Dearborn Campus, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Flint Campus, 1982-1988 (Box 25)
  - Formula Funding, 1993 (Box 25)
  - Funding Model, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Governor's Budget Recommendations, 1985-1994; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Governor's Correspondence Regarding Budget, 1982-1986 (Box 25)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 1990 (Box 25)
  - House Fiscal Agency, 1983-1989 (Box 25)
  - House Fiscal Agency, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Management and Budget, Dept. of, 1982-1993; 6 folders (Box 26)
  - Research Excellence Fund
    - Applications
      - (Depts. of) Chemistry, Biology, Medicine, 1986 (Box 26)
      - College of Engineering, 1987-1993; 5 folders (Box 26)
    - General, 1985-1993; 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee, 1990; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Senate Fiscal Agency, 1986-1993; 4 folders (Box 27)
- Correspondence Files, 1975-1994
  The Correspondence series, 1975-1994 (0.5 linear feet), contains alphabetically arranged correspondence both to and from the Office of Government Relations and Secretary.
  - A-Z (Box 27)
- Evolution of the Office, 1968-1994
  The initial organization and subsequent reorganizations of the Office of Government Relations and Secretary is described in the Evolution of the Office series, 1951-1994 (0.5 linear feet). Although materials in previous accessions describe the office activities more completely, the researcher may find the office organizational charts and staff meeting minutes in this series useful. The series is arranged chronologically, and ends with a small subseries of materials from Interim Secretary of the University Harold Johnson, who held the position from July 1994 to December 1994.
  - State Relations and Planning/Office of Vice President
    - Fauri, Fedele, 1981 (Box 28)
    - General, 1968-1974; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Organizational Charts, 1970-1973 (Box 28)
  - VP for State Relations and Secretary of the University
    - General, 1974-1984; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Organizational Charts, 1974-1983 (Box 28)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
    - General, 1984-1994 (Box 28)
    - Organizational Charts, 1985-1992 (Box 28)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1986-1992 (Box 28)
  - Interim Secretary of the University, Harold Johnson, July 1994-December 1994
    - Detroit Rackham Focus Group, 1993 (Box 28)
    - General, July 1994-December 1994 (Box 28)
    - Rodriguez, Joe (Personnel RESTRICTED until January 1, 2024 removed to vault storage), 1994 (Box 28)
- Audio-Visual Materials, 1980-1984
  The Audio-Visual Materials series, 1980-1984 (0.2 linear feet), contains 35mm slides used in presentations to defeat the Tisch Amendment and other tax limitation proposals. These presentations were coordinated by Peter Pellerito, Assistant to the Vice President for State Relations. A script and audio cassette tape accompany the slides.
  - Michigan Odyssey, circa 1980s; 101 35mm slides color (Box 28)
  - Proposal C slide show, 1984; 58 35mm slides color; 1 audiocassettes (Box 28)
    (includes printed script)
  - Proposal D (Tisch Amendment) slide show, 1980; 139 35mm slides color (Box 28)
- Washington Office Files, 1984-1999
  The Washington Office Files series, 1984-1999 (5.0 linear feet), contains correspondence, memoranda and reports which document the wide variety of activities and interests for which the Washington, D.C. office is responsible. The files were transferred by Tom Butts, executive director of the university's Washington office and associate Vice President for Government Relations and the bulk of the documentation is from the 1990s. Topics covered include budgets and appropriations; research partnerships between the university and government agencies; indirect costs charged against research grants (including an audit of U of M charges); and tax and tuition legislation. Much of the documentation within this series pertains to the student loan advocacy activities performed by Tom Butts. Butts was a national authority in student loan reform and direct student lending, and the records detail his membership and involvement on committees and in organizations devoted to student loan issues.
  - 1984-1999
    - A.C.S.F.A. (Advisory Committee on Student Financial Assistance), 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - A.R.P.A. (Advanced Research Projects Agency) Proposals, 1993 (Box 29)
    - Ability to Benefit Roundtable, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Ad Hoc Tax Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 29)
    - Agenda for the University of Michigan, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
    - American Association of Universities, 1986-1987 (Box 29)
    - American Council on Education (ACE)
      - Middle Income Task Force, 1989 (Box 29)
      - Reauthorization Task Force, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Appreciated Property, 1989-1990 (Box 29)
    - Appreciated Property Working Group, 1989-1990 (Box 29)
    - Appropriations
      - 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - 1989-1992, 7 folders (Box 29)
    - Biomedical Research Grants, 1992 (Box 29)
    - Budget, 1990-1993; 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Budget Appropriations, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Budget-Ways and Means, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Bush Commencement, 1991 (Box 29)
    - Bush Education, 2000; 1991 (Box 29)
    - Business and Financial Management Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 29)
    - Cafeteria Plans, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
    - Cavazos, Lauro (Secretary of Education), 1989 (Box 29)
    - C.B.A. (Consumer Banking Association) Lobby Day, 1993 (Box 29)
    - C.B.O. (Congressional Budget Office) Numbers, 1995 (Box 29)
    - Center on Technology in Education-Jerome Johnston, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Clean Air Act, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Committee for Education Funding Awards Dinner, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Competitiveness Bill, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
    - Congressional Staff Visit, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Congressional Visits, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
    - Consolidation Loans, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Crockett, Larry (mainly re: Trade Adjustment Assistance Center), 1987-1993 (Box 29)
    - Crockett, Larry (mainly re: Flint Community Stabilization and Revitalization Proposal), 1991-1992 (Box 29)
    - Default Cost Sharing, 1994 (Box 30)
    - Default Regulations, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
    - Defense Conversion, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Department of Defense-Open Competition, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Department of Energy, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Direct Student Loans and Lending, 1991-1999; 8 folders (Box 30)
    - Direct Loans-Clinton Press Conference, 1994 (Box 30)
    - Duderstadt, James J., 1988 (Box 30)
    - Earmarking Hearing, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Education-Equity and Excellence Act, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Education Goals, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
    - Energy-Academic Partnerships, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Environment, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (E.P.A.)
      - EPA Center, Bay City, 1992 (Box 30)
      - UM School of Natural Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 30)
    - Facilities, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Federal Facilities Project, Michigan, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Luncheon, 1986 (Box 30)
    - Gephardt (Senator Richard) Honors Convocation, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Glee Club Orient Tour, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
    - GPO (Government Publications Office) Funding-Library, 1992 (Box 30)
    - Graduate Reauthorizations, 1984-1989 (Box 30)
    - Graduate Student Assistant Tuition Waivers, 1988-1989 (Box 30)